https://www.allterrain4wd.org.au/privacy-policy/

Information that is gathered from visitors
In common with other websites, log files are stored on the web server saving details such as the visitor’s IP address, browser type, referring page and time of visit.
Cookies may be used to remember visitor preferences when interacting with the website.
Where registration is required, the visitor’s email and a username will be stored on the server.
How the Information is used
The information is used to enhance the vistor’s experience when using the website to display personalised content and possibly advertising.
E-mail addresses will not be sold, rented or leased to 3rd parties.
E-mail may be sent to inform you of news of our services or offers by us or our affiliates.
Consent
By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its terms.
Log Files
allterrain4wd.org.au follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this and a part of hosting services’ analytics. The information collected by log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movement on the website, and gathering demographic information. Our Privacy Policy was created with the help of the Privacy Policy Generator and the Online Privacy Policy Generator.
Third Party Privacy Policies
allterrain4wd’s Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options.
You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options. To know more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, it can be found at the browsers’ respective websites. What Are Cookies?
Children’s Information
Another part of our priority is adding protection for children while using the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.
allterrain4wd does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our website, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.
Recent Posts
4×4 Tyres – Why Are They Important?
4WD Roof Racks – Where to Get the Best Deals
Off-Road Driving Basics
Off-Roading Tips – 4 Essential Things You Should Know About Off-Roading
Some Sand Driving Tips That Work Wonders!
4×4 Tyres – Why Are They Important?
4WD Roof Racks – Where to Get the Best Deals
Off-Road Driving Basics
Off-Roading Tips – 4 Essential Things You Should Know About Off-Roading
Some Sand Driving Tips That Work Wonders!
